http://www.rothgerber.com/privacy-policy

×Close
Our Privacy Policy has recently changed. Please click here to read the new terms.
12/09/2020
Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie Attorney Receives Tom Karas Criminal Justice Award
12/03/2020
Real Estate Attorney Jack Mankamyer Joins Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie
Date Last Modified: Dec. 30, 2019
This Policy applies only to information that is collected on the Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie LLP Website.  If you have hired us to be your lawyer, our privacy and confidentiality obligations are described in our engagement letter with you.  This policy only addresses what happens if you visit us online and this policy does not apply to information collected by:
•    us offline or through any other means; or
•    any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.
Regardless, Your privacy is important to you and to Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie. With this notice, we want to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our Website.
1.    The information we collect
We do not collect personally identifiable information about you - such as your name, address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address, etc. – unless you choose to fill out a ‘Contact Us’ form, found on many of the pages of the site or to email us directly.
2.    How we normally use Non-Personal Information
We do automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our site – such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. In addition to collecting Personal Information from you, we may use a variety of technologies that automatically collect Non-Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is information about you or your use of the Website that does not identify you personally. This includes your domain server, device type, web browser, the operating system or platform you use to access the Website as well as referrer data identifying the web pages you visited prior to and after visiting the Website and your movement and activity within the Website. We use aggregated non-personally identifiable information to analyze and improve the design, use and content of the Website
In the ordinary course, we use personal information you provide solely to respond to your inquiry or process an application form you have completed on various sections of our Web site.
Any data gathered will be shared, if appropriate, with any of the offices of Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie and any third parties who provide services on our behalf. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred within our offices in the United States (or outside of the country).  If we transfer your information outside of the United States, you should know that the applicable data protection laws may differ, and by visiting this site, you expressly agree to such transfer.
3.    How we normally use Personal Information
We use your Personal Information to fulfill the purpose(s) for which you have provided it, to respond to and process your specific requests for information, and for any other purpose that we disclose to you at the time we collect your Personal Information. We may use some Personal Information to send you updates, news, conferences, or other information, which we deem may be important to our visitors. We also may share Personal Information with our contractors and service providers whom we retain to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep Personal Information confidential and to use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
If you provide Personal Information to us via the Website in the context of an event that Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie LLP sponsors or hosts with another company, you may also be providing the Personal Information to the co-sponsor or co-host. For purposes of events, we will obtain your consent to share your first and last name and applicable company name with our co-sponsor or co-host. For example, if we hold an event with an accounting firm, we would give the accounting firm your registration information to allow them to track reservations.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may be required to provide Personal Information in response to a court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We may release certain Personal Information when we believe that such a release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Privacy Policy, to abide by our professional ethical responsibilities, or to protect the interests and/or safety of the Firm, its employees or its clients. We may also share Personal Information in the event of a merger, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Firm’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which Personal Information held by the Firm is among the assets transferred.
4.    Collection of information by third-parties
If you access the Website from a third party platform, such as a Social Networking Site , you may be required to also read and accept the terms and conditions and privacy policy of that third party. The Firm is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties, and you should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies.
5.    Cookies, and to enable or disable them
Our Website uses automatic data collection technologies to obtain the Non-Personal Information described in this policy. Specifically, our Website uses browser cookies. A browser cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.  We do not use flash cookies or web beacons.
When we use cookies, we do this to help make our site work, to improve your experience on the Website, and to allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our site – without being able to identify individual users of the Website.
6.    Disabling/enabling cookies
Our Website incorporates security to allow you to disabling/enable cookies.  You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled. For further information about disabling or blocking cookies, please visit AboutCookies.org.
7.    Data and Information Security
Our Website incorporates commercially reasonable security measures designed to reduce the risk of improper access to the online information that we collect. We cannot guarantee the privacy of personal information you transmit over the web or that may be collectable in transit by others, including contractors who provide services to us.  For this reason, you also need to use security measures such as anti-virus and anti-hacking tools, to protect the security of your personal information.  Further, our Website and policy are based in the United States. Your Personal Information will be used and stored in the United States, where data protection and privacy rules may differ from the level of protection available in other parts of the world, including Canada, Mexico and the European Union.
8.    Special Note About Children
Our Website is a general audience site that is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information (defined below) from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not provide any information about yourself on this Website or use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at: webinfo@LRRC.com.
9.    Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of the State of California to request from certain businesses with whom the California resident has an established business relationship a list of all third parties to which the business, during the immediately preceding calendar year, has disclosed certain personally identifiable information for direct marketing purposes. For more information on how to submit a request please click here.  We do not track your on-line activity across other websites, nor do we knowingly permit any third-parties to conduct online tracking of you while you are visiting our Website. Consequently, we do not respond to your browser’s Do Not Track signal or technologies that you may have implemented in your web browser.
10.    Your Feedback
If you would like to contact us for any reason about this Privacy Policy or our privacy procedures and practices, please send an email to: webinfo@LRRC.com with the subject heading “Privacy Policy” or write to Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie LLP at: 201 E. Washington, Suite 1200, Phoenix, AZ 85004, Attn: Privacy Policy.
11.    Revisions to our Privacy Policy
To improve the services it can offer you, Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie LLP may choose to expand its capabilities for obtaining information about users in the future. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will update the “Date Last Modified” and such changes will be effective upon posting.
We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have. Please be sure to check this page before proceeding to use our Website. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will always use your Personal Information in accordance with the version of the Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you give your express consent for us to do otherwise.
Remote Access
/
About
/
Events
/
Pro Bono
/
201 East Washington Street Suite 1200 · Phoenix, AZ 85004 · 602.262.5311
© Copyright 2020 All Rights Reserved. Lewis Roca Rothgerber Christie LLP.
- An Am Law 200 commercial law firm for handling complex matters
